Guide to the Ray Stevens Ashbery papers, [1930-1971?].
Ashbery, Ray Stevens papers, [1930-1971?].
- Series II. Subject files, 1948-1962. Assembly files, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Dean, Richard E., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Diefendorf Commission, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Disability Benefits Law, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dryden - Flood Creek, 1956, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dryden - Signal Light, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Eberhardt, Constance K, memos, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Education - Mentally Retarded Children, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Education, 1955, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Education - Central School, 1955, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Education - Cornell, 1955, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Education - Ithaca Area, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Education, Ithaca City Schools, 1957, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Education - School Finance Commission, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Education - State University, 1955, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Education - Teacher's Union, 1955, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Education - Television, 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Election Law 157a, 1955, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Election Laws, 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Empire Livestock, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Engineering, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Engineering, 1956, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Equalization, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Equalization, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Firearms, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Florida Trip - Unemployment Ins. Mtgs., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Ethics, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Fyr-Larm, 1955, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - George Junior Republic, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - G.L.F. Correspondence 1954, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - G.L.F. Grant 1953, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - G.L.F. Vic Underwood, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Governor's Message, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Gragg, William - meeting Jan. 23, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Groton - Jacobs, re School Taxes, 1956, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Groves - Milton and Ursula, Labor Dept., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Harness Racing, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Hatch Bill, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Public Health Committee, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Health, 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 39-40)
  - Health - 1955 - Psychology, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Health Insurance - State Employees, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Highways, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 43-44)
  - Highway - RA's speech Bar Association, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Highway Commission, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Highway Commission RA speech, WHCU Oct., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Highway Finance Commission, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Highways General, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Highways Good Roads 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Highways - North-South Expressway, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Highways - Route 38, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Highways - Safety 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Highways - Safety 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Highways - Safety 1955, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Highways - Tompkins County, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Highways - Tompkins County, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Highways - Tompkins County, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Highways - Tompkins County Rt. 13 By-pass, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Highways - Thruway, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Highways - Temporary Highway Finance, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Highway Trucks, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Highways, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Home - Feb., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Home - week of Mar. 4, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Take Home, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Horseheads Rotary Club Meeting - Oct., 1956 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Housing 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Housing, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Hurst, Elmer, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Insurance - Compulsory 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Invitations 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Invitations 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Invitations 1955, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Ithaca Annexation, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Ithaca Area School Study, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Ithaca Power Squadron, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Judiciary Committee book 1959, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Justice Court Topics, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Knailand [?], William Senator, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Labor 1953, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Labor 1954, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Labor - Migrant, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Birth Certificate - Clarence E. Lamb, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Land - Subdivision, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - League of Women Voters, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Legislation Pending, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Manual 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Manual, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Legislation Pending, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Legislative Summary, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Long Island Transit, 1951-1954 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Maps - Senatorial and Congressional, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Meetings 1957, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Meetings 1957, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Metcalf, George, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Metcalf - Albany Kernels, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous 1955, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Motor Vehicles - Frommer 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Motor Vehicles, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Motor Vehicles 1955, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Motor Vehicles Compulsory Insurance, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Motor Vehicles Committee, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Motor Vehicles General, 1952-1953 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Multiple Dwelling Law, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Multiple Housing 1955, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Multiple Legislative Service, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - News Release, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - News Releases, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 32-33)
  - New York State Farm Organization, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Niagara Power, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Newfield Fire District, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Newman, Charles - Bills Requested, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Niagara Power 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Niagara Power Authority, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Parks, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Parking - Off Street, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Passes, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Passes, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Passes, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Pierson, Clara T., 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Podiatrists Bill, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Port of Authority, 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Proposed Legislation 1957, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Railroads 1955, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Railroads (Full Crew) 1955, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Albany - Reapportionment, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Red Book, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Red Book 1955-56, 1954-1957 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Redistricting, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Reference Material, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Resolution - Federal, State, Municipal Relationships, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Release Material, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Republican Committee New York State 1, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Republican State Committee, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Republican Party - Legislative Program 1957, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Republican Club - Tompkins County, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Request for Bills, May, after Session, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Retirement, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Rush, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Rush, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - St. Lawrence, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - St. Lawrence Seaway, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Sampson Air Force Base, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Scholarships, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Scrap Book, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Smith, O'Connell, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Social Security, 1954, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Social Security Retirement, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Social Welfare, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Speakers Releases, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Speeches, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 20-21)
  - Speeches, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Special Session, Legislature, Nov. 11, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Special Sessions - Assembly, June 10, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - State Affairs Committee, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - State Lands, Abandonment Roads, Parks, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - State Police 1955, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Sunday Law, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Taber, John, Hon., 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Taber, John, 1954-55, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Taxes, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Taxes, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Taxes, Equalization 1955, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Telephone 1954, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Title Association, New York State, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Tompkins County Republican Picnic, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Thruway, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Trailers - Assessment, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Trapp, Stella M., 1956-1967 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Trucks 1955, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Truck Mileage Tax - Correspondence, 195419-55 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Trumansburg - Postmaster 1954-55, 1952-1954 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Trumansburg - Social Security, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Unemployment Insurance - Floor Debate, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 44-45)
  - untitled, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Veterans' Administration, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Volunteer Firemen, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Wedell, Carl 1954, 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Welfare, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Wicks, Senator 1954, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 52-53)
  - Youth Bureau, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Armand Adams, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Aged, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture - Milk, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture - New York State Grange, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Albany Kernels, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Annexation - Renwick tract - City of Ithaca, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Ashbery, Ray Stephens, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Ashbery - Bills, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Ashbery - News Releases, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Ashbery - Travel Expense Vouchers, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Assembly Floor, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Associated Industries of New York, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Automobile Association - New York State, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Banks - Savings, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Bingo, 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 18-20)
  - Caveney, William Henry, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Chapman, James E., 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 23-24)
  - Chatfield, Charles, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Chiefs of Police, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Chiropractic, Inc., American Bureau of, 1954-1956 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Colbert, J. Reed, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Conservation, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 29-30)
  - Constitutional Amendments, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 32-33)
  - Constitutional Convention Questions, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Cornell - Admissions, 1953-1955 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Cornell - Applicants, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Cornell University, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 37-38)
  - Council of Churches, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Courts, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Temporary Commission on the Courts, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Courts - Youths, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Crispell Truck Tax, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Diefendorf Commission, 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 44-45)
  - Donavan, E. Craig, 1954-55 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Dotson, Archie T., 1955 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Education, 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 48-50)
  - Education - Enlarged City School, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Education - Gragg, W. L., 1957 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Education - Heald Commission, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Education - Ithaca, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Education - Scholarships, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Education - Trumansburg, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Elections, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Empire Livestock Marketing Cooperative, Inc., 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 58-59)
  - Empire State Chamber of Commerce, 1954-1955 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Engineering Laws, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Episcopal Church - Women's Auxiliary, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Equalization Rates, 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Farm Bureau, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Fernow, Howard, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Flood Control, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Follow-Up, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Forest Preserve, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Forest Industries Committee, New York, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 4-H Club - County, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 4-H Club Dinner, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Friday Afternoon Session Memoranda, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Funeral Director, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - G - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Grange League Federation -. C. L. Dickinson, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 12-13)
  - Governor's Messages, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Health, 1954-1956 (Box 12, Folder 15-16)
  - Housing, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 17-18)
  - Insurance, 1954-1955 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Invitations, 1955-57 (Box 12, Folder 20-21)
  - Ithaca, City of, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Ithaca Central Labor Union, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Ithaca College, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Ithaca Taxpayers Association, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Ithaca Water System - H. L. Cosline, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Joint Legislative Committee to Study Laws on Matrimony, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Jones, Eugene B., 1956 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Judiciary, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Labor, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 30-31)
  - Lansing Vote, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - League of Women Voters, 1949-1957 (Box 12, Folder 33-34)
  - Lee, D. Boardman, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Legislative Hopper, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 36-37)
  - Legislative Questionnaire - Post Standard, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Mayors Conference - New York State, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Meetings, 1956- (Box 12, Folder 41-42)
  - Metcalf, Senator - News Releases, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Migrant Labor, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Migrant Labor - New York State Joint Legislative Committee, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Motor-boating Bills, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Motor Vehicles, 1951-1957 (Box 12, Folder 48-49)
  - Motor Vehicle - Cross View Mirrors, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Motor Vehicles - Compulsory Insurance, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Motor Vehicle - Headlight Dimmers, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Motor Vehicles - Insurance, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Motor Vehicles - Licenses, 1955-1958 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Motor Vehicles - Safety, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Multiple Residence Law, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Newfield, Town of, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - News Releases, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 58-59)
  - New York Good Roads Association, 1954-1957 (Box 12, Folder 60-61)
  - New York Business Development Corporation, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - New York, City of, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - New York Red Book, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - New York State Automobile Association, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - New York State Banker, 1956-1957 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - New York State Bar Association, 1954-1956 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - New York State Grange, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - New York State Journal, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Niagara Power, 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 70-71)
  - Panther Mountain Dam (Black River Valley), 1955 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Permanent Personal Registration, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Public Health, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Regents Scholarship, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Releases - Speaker, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Rent Control, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Republican Party - Legislative Program, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Republican Party - State, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Republican Party - Tompkins County, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Republican State Committee, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Retirement - Teachers, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Roe, J. Russell (Zoning Laws), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Safety, 1954-1956 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Division of Safety News Bulletin, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Sales Tax, 1951, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Sampson Air Force Base, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Savings Banks, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Sheriff - Howard Harvey, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Social Security, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Social Welfare Law, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Social Welfare, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - South Hill Civic Association, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Speech Material, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - St. Lawrence Seaway and Power Project, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - State Government, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - State Police, Division of, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - State University of New York, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Steuben Society of New York, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Stevenson, H. A. (Cornell Alumni News), 1956 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Supervisors' Association, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Swartwood, Richard C., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - T - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Talking Books for the Blind, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Tax - Gas, Fuel, Assessment, Income, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Taxes, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Thruway Authority, New York State, 1954-1956 (Box 13, Folder 36-37)
  - Tompkins County, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Tompkins County - Board of Supervisors, 1955-1957 (Box 13, Folder 39-41)
  - Tompkins County Grange Meeting, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Tompkins County Hotel and Restaurant Association, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Tompkins County - Lansing Vote, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Track Motor Cars, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Trailers, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Trapp, Stella M., 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Treman, Allan H., 1955 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Truck Tax, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Truck Tax (New York Weight Distance Tax), 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Trumansburg, Village of, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Tuning Fork, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Ulysses, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Ulysses, Town of - Town Tax Collectors Bond, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1955-1958 (Box 13, Folder 55-59)
  - University of the State of New York, 1955-1957 (Box 13, Folder 60-61)
  - Veterans' Affairs, Division of, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Voluntary Firemen, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Voluntary Firemen - Joint Legislative Committee on Fire Laws, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Watchdog Commission, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Weekly Bulletin, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Welfare, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - WHCU Letters to the Editor, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Whitford, Davey T., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Wiretapping - Joint Legislative Committee to Study Illegal Interception, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Women's Legislative Meetings, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1954-1957 (Box 13, Folder 73-75)
  - Youth Commission, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Accountants, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Adoption, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Albany - Jan.-Mar., 1959 (Box 14, Folder 4-12)
  - Albany - Gasoline Tax, 1959, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Albany - Hotel Expense, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Albany - Papers to File, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 15-16)
  - Albany - Reference Files, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 17-25)
  - Albany - Room Reservations, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Albany - Special Session, July 1, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Amendments, 1959, 1961, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Animals, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Ashbery, 1959 - Miscellaneous Assembly Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Ashbery - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Ashbery - News Releases, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Ashbery - Personal Miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Ashbery - News Releases, 1059 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Ashbery - Prefiled Bills, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Associated Industries of New York State, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Atomic Energy, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Aviation, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Banks, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 39-40)
  - Bar Association, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Barge Canal, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Bingo, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Brown, Walter, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Budget, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 45-47)
  - Budget Questionnaire, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Children, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Chiropractors, 1957-1959 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - CIO Council, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Citizens Union of City of New York, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Civil Service, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Comparative Negligence, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Conservation, 1956-1959 (Box 14, Folder 55-56)
  - Convention - Rochester, Aug. 25-26, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Corcoran, William R. (Public Service Commission - Civil Service Commission), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Cornell, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Cornell Admissions, 1958-1959, 1957-1960 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Cornell - Proposed Legislation School District exemptions of real property, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Cornell (Retired Employees Health Insurance), 1959 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Tompkins County Council of Churches, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Courts, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
  - Court Reform, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
  - Crime 1958, 1957-1959 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Diefendorf Commission, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Education, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 7-10)
  - Education - Cornell University 1958, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Education - Groton Meeting, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Education - State 1958, 1957-1959 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Education - Tompkins County, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Election, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Empire Livestock Marketing Cooperative, Inc., 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Empire State Chamber of Commerce, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 17-18)
  - Employment, Division of, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Engineering, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Farm Bureau, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Finger Lakes Association, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Firelaws, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Flood Control, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - General Laws, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Governor's Messages, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Governor - News Releases, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Health, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Health (Imitation Food Products and Problems), 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Public Health, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Heck - Speaker, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Highway Commission, 1959, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Highways, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Highways - Route 38 (Tioga County), 1958 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Highways - State, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Highways - Tompkins County, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Home Remedies and Pharmacy, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Housing, 1957-1959 (Box 15, Folder 38-39)
  - Industrial Bulletin, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Insurance, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
  - Insurance - Life Underwriters, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 5-7)
  - Ithaca Chamber of Commerce, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
  - Ithaca - Flood Control, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Ithaca - Gambling Investigation, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 11)